Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New business records, 1924-2007 and undated, bulk 1980-1989 RL.00731
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Companies Files, 1946-2005 and undated, 72 boxes
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust
    - Basic information, 1985 (Box 55)
    - First and second quarter analyses, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Leave-behind book, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Presentation, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Situational analysis, 1982 (Box 55)
  - Marks & Spencer
    - Clippings, 1984-1986 (Box 56)
    - Presentation, including campaign notes, 1987 (Box 56)
  - Mary Kay Cosmetics
    - General files, 1981-1983 (Box 56)
  - MasterCard
    - General files, 1984 (Box 56)
    - Clippings, 1983 (Box 56)
    - Consumer interview questions, 1984 (Box 56)
    - Consumer interviews--Atlanta, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Consumer interviews--Chicago, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Consumer interviews--New York, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Scripts from consumer tapes, 1984 (Box 57)
  - Max Factor
    - Consumer interviews, 1985, 2 folders (Box 57)
  - McGraw-Edison Company
    - General files, 1955 Apr.-1965 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 57)
  - McNeil
    - Choosing a Partner presentation, 1985 (Box 57)
  - Mennen
    - General files, 1987 (Box 57)
  - Mentholatum Company
    - General files, 1954 Oct.-1961 Jan. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 57)
  - Meredith Publishing Company
    - General files, 1954 Oct.-1962 (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 57)
  - Merillat Industries
    - Taking Merillat to New Places presentation, 1992 (Box 57)
  - Merrill Lynch
    - Credentials presentation files, 1985 (Box 57)
    - How to Win Merrill Lynch: The Short Course, 1985 (Box 57)
  - Metro
    - Promotional brochure, undated (Box 57)
  - Michigan State Lottery
    - Presentation book, 1983 (Box 57)
    - Response, You'll Love Our Winning Ways, 1992 (Box 57a)
  - Microsoft
    - New business presentation, 1983 (Box 57)
  - Midas
    - Clippings, 1985-1987 (Box 57)
    - Overview, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Quarterly reports, 1987 (Box 57)
  - Midwest Bell (Ameritech)
    - New business presentation, 1983 (Box 57)
  - Midwest Bell (Ameritech)
    - New business research presentation, 1983 (Box 58)
  - Miles Laboratories
    - General files, 1964 Apr.-1967 Aug. (Bill Torrey files) (Box 58)
  - Miller Brewing Company
    - American Beer Market Review & forecast, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Analysis of Above-Premium Beer Drinkers, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Beer advertising regulations, 1982-1984 (Box 58)
    - Beer buying system, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Beer category competitive environment, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Beer industry articles, 1978-1985, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Beer market review and forecast, 1983 (Box 58)
    - Beer print-ads, 1968-1983 (Box 58)
    - Beer print advertising, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Brewing strategic research, 1987 (Box 58)
    - Bud Lite marketing plan, 1989 (Box 59)
    - Clippings, beer specific, 1968-1983 (Box 59)
    - Clippings, 1989 (Box 59)
    - Competitive ads, 1968-1976 (Box 59)
    - Confidentiality agreement, undated (Box 59)
    - Consumer information, 1981-1984 (Box 59)
    - Counterattack presentation, undated (Box 59)
    - Dry briefing, 1988 (Box 59)
    - Dry campaign ideas, undated (Box 59)
    - High Life
      - Bartender interviews, 1984, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Campaign sketches, circa 1984 (Box 59)
      - Case file, 1984-1985 (Box 59)
      - Consumer taste tests, 1984 (Box 59)
      - Counter Attack presentation, 1984 (Box 59)
      - Creative Department miscellaneous files, 1984 (Box 60)
      - Creative presentation (Miller Time rhyme search), 1984 (Box 60)
      - Creative strategy proposal, circa 1984 (Box 60)
      - Credentials presentation, 1984 (Box 60)
      - Marketing review, 1984, 2 folders (Box 60)
      - Miller High Life and U.S. beer industry background information, 1984 (Box 60)
      - Miller High Life versus Bud Lite file, 1984 (Box 60)
      - Miller Man campaign sketches, circa 1984 (Box 60)
      - New business presentation, 1984 (Box 60)
      - Presentation, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Reasons for High Life Sales Decline, 1980-1984 (Box 60)
      - Television spot scripts, 1984 (Box 60)
    - Historical information (1850s), undated (Box 60)
    - How to Structure the Ideation Process, 1988 (Box 60)
    - Internal briefing, 1988 (Box 60)
    - JWT expenses, 1984 (Box 60)
    - Matilda Bay Cooler
      - Background review, 1986 (Box 60)
      - Borrowed Heritage scripts, 1987 (Box 60)
      - Focus groups, 1986-1987 (Box 60)
      - Market visits, 1987 (Box 60)
      - Positioning, 1987 (Box 61)
      - Project Tranquility research, 1987 (Box 61)
      - Test research, 1987 (Box 61)
    - Media spending, 1975-1983 (Box 61)
    - Miller at a Crossroads: A Discussion of How to Manage the Miller Franchise of Brands, 1987 (Box 61)
    - Miller Legacy presentation, undated (Box 61)
    - Miller Lite
      - 18-24 Year-Olds Today, undated (Box 61)
      - Analyzing Lite Beer Drinkers in Different Age Groups, undated (Box 61)
      - Brand Positioning and Strategic Discussions, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Business briefing, 1988, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
      - Ex-Athletes Used in Commercials, 1986-1988 (Box 61)
      - Media issues, undated (Box 61)
      - New Growth for Miller Lite, 1988, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - One Journey Two Tracks presentation, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Per Miller Lite: The Löwenbräu Contemporary Adult Presentation and Stop Making Sense Videotape, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Perceptions of regular versus lite drinkers, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Planning: Key issues--objectives and strategies 1988 (Box 62)
      - Positioning and strategic alternatives, 1988, 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Preliminary Miller Lite positionings, 1988 (Box 62)
      - Research file, 1988, 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Personnel information, 1984 (Box 62)
    - Premium beer franchise marketing plan recommendations, 1988 (Box 62)
    - Present a Totally New Idea in Sports Syndication for Miller Beer, 1973 (Box 62)
    - Project Ice focus groups, 1986 (Box 62)
    - Project Near overview, 1980 (Box 62)
    - Project Tranquility brand updates, 1987 (Box 62)
    - Regional managers meeting, 1988 (Box 62)
    - Strategic assessment of Miller mainstream brands, undated (Box 62)
    - Syndicated study, Burt Reynolds testimonial campaign, 1981-1984 (Box 62)
    - Synergy discussion, 1988 (Box 62)
    - Targeting Your Adult Beer Drinkers, undated (Box 62)
    - Taste test file, 1984, 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Traditional values and youth file, 1984 (Box 63)
    - Trends in Alcohol Knowledge and Drinking Patterns Among Students Who Visited Daytona Beach, Fla., During Spring Break, 1983 (Box 63)
    - U.S. beer market, 1981 (Box 63)
  - Millicom Incorporated
    - General files, 1985 (Box 63)
  - Milliken
    - General files, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Mobil Chemical Company
    - General files, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Mobile Home Manufacturers Association
    - General files, 1962 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 63)
  - Monet
    - General files, 1983 (Box 63)
  - Montec Group
    - General files, 1982 (Box 63)
  - Moran & Tucker
    - General files, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Morgan Stanley
    - General files, 1986 (Box 63)
    - Annual report, 1986 (Box 63)
    - Business journalists' attitude toward current issues in investment banking, 1986 (Box 63)
    - Consumer interview files, 1985 (Box 63)
    - Initial Observations and Recommendations, 1985 (Box 63)
    - Investment Banking and Morgan Stanley circa 1986 (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous files, 1981-1985 (Box 63)
    - Presentations, 1986-1989, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Ranking clips, 1985-1986 (Box 64)
    - Surveys presentation, 1985 (Box 64)
    - Telling the Morgan Stanley Story, 1985 (Box 64)
  - Motorola
    - General files, 1987 (Box 64)
  - Mott's
    - Agency briefing, 1992, 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Mrs. Paul's
    - Consumer interviews, undated (Box 64)
  - Murine Company
    - General files, 1955 Sep.-1963 Mar. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 64)
  - Murani
    - International file, 1981 (Box 64)
    - Presentation book, 1979-1980 (Box 64)
    - Storyboards, 1981 (Box 64)
    - Tearsheets, 1980 (Box 64)
  - Nabisco
    - Advertising Campaigns for Wheat Thins, Better Cheeses, 1985 (Box 65)
    - Advertising Cookies and Crackers, presentation to Japanese Biscuit Association, 1983 (Box 65)
    - Company overview, 1985 (Box 65)
    - Cookies and crackers file, 1984 (Box 65)
    - Del Monte file, 1987 (Box 65)
    - Credentials presentation file, 1983-1985 (Box 65)
    - Gourmet food articles, 1984 (Box 65)
    - Planter's Peanuts market review, 1983 (Box 65)
    - Planter's: Point of view about Planter's snacks, 1984 (Box 65)
    - Primary Cracker Category Imagery, Categorization, and Usage, 1984 (Box 65)
    - R.J. Reynolds file, 1987-1988 (Box 65)
    - Underlying Attitudes presentation, undated (Box 65)
  - Napa Naturals
    - New business presentation, 1983 (Box 66)
  - National Fisheries
    - General files, 1946 Oct.-1957 June (Milton Moskowitz files>) (Box 66)
  - National Enquirer
    - General files, 1987-1989 (Box 66)
    - Confidential memorandum, 1989 (Box 66)
    - Fact sheet, 1986-1987 (Box 66)
    - Getting to the Core of America presentation, 1987 (Box 66)
    - Reasons for Frequency of Readership, 1987 (Box 66)
  - Nestlé
    - General files, 1949 Aug.-1958 July (Bill Torrey files) (Box 66)
    - General files, 1958 Aug.-1963 Oct. (Bill Torrey files) (Box 66)
    - Briefing on Nestlé Ice Cream Company and the frozen dessert category, 1993 (Box 66)
    - Discussion of JWT with Nestlé Company Incorporated, 1958 (Howard Henderson's copy) (Box 66)
    - Presentation, 1993 (Box 66)
  - New Holland Machine Company
    - General files, 1955 June-1961 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 66)
  - New York State Department of Economic Development
    - General files, 1982-1988, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Annual strategies, 1988 (Box 67)
    - Biographical profiles, 1987 (Box 67)
    - Bumper stickers, undated (Box 67)
    - JWT presentation, 1987 (Box 67)
    - JWT questionnaire response, 1987, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Logo used for Department of Commerce, undated (Box 67)
    - Request for proposal, 1987, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Summary of media plans and responses by campaign, 1987 (Box 67)
    - Travel attitudes and behaviors, 1987 (Box 68)
    - Travel benchmark study, 1987, 2 folders (Box 68)
  - New York State Lottery
    - General files, 1987-1988 (Box 68)
    - Advertising agency review, 1987 and 1993, 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Advertising agency review questionnaire, 1993 (Box 68)
    - Briefing document, 1993 (Box 68)
    - Information packet, 1987 (Box 68)
    - Radio TV (television) reports, 1987 (Box 68)
    - Request for proposal, 1988 (Box 68)
  - New York Stock Exchange
    - General files, 1959 Feb.-1960 July (Bill Torrey files) (Box 68)
  - New York World's Fair
    - General files, 1960 June-1963 Sep. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 68)
    - Publications, 1961 Sep.-1963 Sep. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 69)
  - Nextel
    - [JWT credentials presentation, 2003: Moved to Restricted Materials] (Box 69)
  - Nike
    - Background for 1993 Presentation of Odyssey to Nike, 1993 (Box 69)
  - No Nonsense
    - Presentation book, 1994 Sep. 29 (Box 69)
  - North American Philips Corporation
    - [JWT-USA-- North American Philips Corporation--Norelco, circa 1986-1987: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 69)
    - Norelco presentation, circa 1987 (Box 69)
  - North American Treaty Organization (NATO)
    - Creative presentation, circa 1982 (Box 69)
  - North Carolina Blue Cross
    - General files, 1954 Nov. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 69)
  - Northeastern Communications (NEC)
    - Building Momentum, 1994 (Box 69)
    - Credentials presentation, 1994 Mar. 3 (Box 69)
    - Presentation book, 1994 (Box 69)
    - So What is the Big Idea? creative presentation, 1994 Mar. 3 (Box 69)
  - Northwest Airlines
    - General files, 1990-1991 (Box 69)
    - Background briefing on Northwest Airlines, 1991 (Box 69)
    - Flight Plan to Success presentation, 1991 (Box 70)
    - How Northwest Should Play Its Trump Card, 1991 (Box 70)
    - International presentation, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Northeast Corridor Air Shuttle Market Briefing, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Presentation, 1991 (Sullivan) (Box 70)
    - Presentation slides, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Trump shuttle presentation, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance
    - General files, 1956 July-1963 (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 70)
  - Novell
    - [Advertising strategy recommendations, 2002: Moved to Restricted Materials] (Box 70)
  - Ocean Spray Cranberries, Incorporated
    - General files, 1954 Apr.-1962 Feb. (Box 70)
  - Old Spice
    - Recommendations for Old Spice, 1986, 2 folders (Box 70)
  - Olive Advisory Board
    - General files, 1957 Nov.-1965 Nov. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 71)
    - Bertolli, 1986-1987 (Box 71)
    - Leave-behind for Acemesa presentation, 1984 (Box 71)
  - Olympic Commemorative Coins
    - Cost proposal, 1988 (Box 71)
    - Technical proposal, 1988, 3 folders (Box 71)
  - Oscar Mayer
    - General files, 1959 Aug.-1963 (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 71)
    - Oscar Mayer Advertising--What's It Worth?, 1988 (Box 71)
    - Thought for Food presentation for Oscar Mayer (charts), 1984 (Box 71)
    - Thought for Food: Review of Consumer Trends Affecting the Future of Food Marketing for Oscar Mayer, 1984 (Box 71)
  - Outboard Marine
    - General files, 1956 Oct.-1964 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 71)
  - Paddington
    - Right Partner for the Right Times, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Pan Am
    - General files, 1962 (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 72)
    - Briefing, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - [JWT-USA--Pan Am briefing, 1988: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 72)
    - Presentation, 1988 (Box 72)
    - Presentation to the New York Society of Airline Security Analysts, 1988 (Box 72)
    - Promotional material, 1988 (Box 72)
    - Shuttle file, circa 1991, 3 folders (Box 72)
  - Parker Pen
    - General files, 1955 Mar.-1961 Nov. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 72)
    - General files, 1960 Oct.-1961 Feb. (Bill Torrey files) (Box 72)
  - PepsiCo
    - Building Worldwide Brands and Business, 1994 (Box 72)
    - Credentials presentation, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Philip Morris
    - Merit--Relighting the Fire presentation, 1986 (Box 73)
  - Phillips Petroleum
    - General files, 1962 June-1964 Apr. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 73)
  - Pillsbury
    - Credentials presentation, 1986 Aug. 5 (Box 73)
    - Nestlé-Toll House frozen cookie dough competitive analysis, 1986 (Box 73)
  - Pineapple Growers Association
    - General files, 1957 Feb.-1957 May (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 73)
  - Pizza Inn
    - Background and presentation, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Planter's Nut and Chocolate Company
    - General files, 1961 (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 73)
  - Playtex
    - Creative review, includes commercial scripts, 1992 (Box 73)
    - Presentation book for Tampax, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Portland Cement Association
    - General files, 1955 June-1957 Sep. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 73)
  - Premier Cruise and Other Cruise Travel
    - General files, 1989-1990 (Box 73)
    - American Hawaii: Competitive Advertising Spending Overview, 1989 (Box 73)
    - Cruise Industry: An Overview, 1989 (Box 73)
    - Sitmar Cruises presentation, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Prudential
    - General files, 1986-1989 (Box 74)
    - Bache file, includes Positioning for the 1990's presentation, 1987-1989 (Box 74)
    - Clippings, 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Competitive advertisements, 1987-1989 (Box 74)
    - Competitive file, 1988, undated (Box 74)
    - Consumer Perception of the Financial Services Market, 1987 (Box 74)
    - Consumer Perceptions of Financial Services and Real Estate, 1988 (Box 74)
    - Credit Card Consumption: A Lifestyle Perspective, 1989 (Box 74)
    - JWT healthcare file, 1987 (Box 74)
    - Project Blue presentation, 1989 Oct. 9, 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Project Peak situation analysis, 1989 (Box 75)
    - Standard & Poor's industry surveys, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Public Service Accounts
    - General files, 1986-1987 (Box 75)
  - Puma
    - Preliminary situation analysis, 1985 (Box 75)
    - Presentation slides, 1985 Aug. 21 (Box 75)
    - Winning team presentation, undated (Box 75)
  - Purdue Fredericks
    - General files, 1988 (Box 75)
    - Betadine medicated douche, SenoKot products, X-Prep in their perspective markets, 1988 Apr. (Box 75)
    - Laxative market studies, 1988 (Box 75)
    - SenoKot Laxatives: clinical and product information, 1988 (Box 75)
    - Study examining opportunities for the laxative market, 1987 (Box 75)
  - Quaker Oats
    - General file, 1949 Dec.-1965 Jan. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 75)
  - Ragu
    - Base spaghetti sauce, 1990 (Box 75)
    - Overview, 1989 (Box 75)
    - Ragu and JWT presentation, 1989 (Box 75)
    - Ragu review, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Ralph Lauren
    - Clippings, 1984 (Box 76)
    - Future presentation, 1989 (Box 76)
  - Rand McNally Company
    - General files, 1962 Mar.-1962 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 76)
  - RCA Corporation
    - General files, 1957-1964 (Milton Moskowitz files), 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Consumer electronics clippings, 1985-1988 (Box 76)
    - Notes on J. Walter Thompson Company, 1959 (Box 76)
  - Reader's Digest
    - General files, 1954 Oct.-1961 Apr. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 76)
  - Rowntree & Company Limited
    - General files, 1954 Apr.-1957 May (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 76)
    - Partnership for Success, 1982 (Box 76)
  - R.T. French
    - General files, 1959 Aug.-1969 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 77)
    - General files, 1987 (Box 77)
    - Bouillon review, 1986 (Box 77)
    - French's Yellow Mustard, case study, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Mustards: competitive creative review, 1986-1987 (Box 77)
    - Project Dynasty, 1986 (Box 77)
    - Yellow mustard wear-out analysis, Be Good to Your Food campaign, 1986 (Box 77)
  - Russell Hobbs
    - General files, 1981 (Box 77)
  - Ryder Trucks
    - Credentials presentation, including JWT annual report, 1982, 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Leverage presentation, undated (Box 77)
    - Management communication audit, 1985 Dec. 16, 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Safeway Stores
    - General files, 1955 Feb.-1961 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 78)
  - Samsonite
    - General files, 1965 Feb.-1969 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 78)
  - Schering-Plough
    - General files, 1987-1988 (Box 78)
    - Allergy, asthma, and sinus products, 1987 (Box 78)
    - Burroughs Welcome, 1988 (Box 78)
    - Interoffice survey results, undated (Box 78)
    - Maybelline
      - General files, 1987 (Box 78)
      - Background, evaluation, plan, undated (Box 78)
      - Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 78)
      - Consumer interviews, 1986, 2 folders (Box 78)
      - The Opportunities in Asia Pacific and Latin America, 1995 (Box 78)
    - Most Recent Hay Fever or Other Allergy: Symptoms Suffered Versus Symptoms Treated, undated (Box 78)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 78)
  - Schlage Lock Company
    - General files, 1956 Nov.-1957 Apr. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 79)
  - Scott Paper Company
    - General files, 1957 Dec.-1962 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 79)
    - JWT-Asia, undated (Box 79)
    - Scott-JWT worldwide partnership, circa 1994 (Box 79)
  - Seagram's
    - General files, 1956 Sep.-1959 Sep. (Bill Torrey files) (Box 79)
    - General files, 1966 July (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 79)
  - Sears
    - Credit card presentation, 1984, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Seven-Eleven
    - Advertising planning recommendation, 1988 (Box 79)
    - Change: Risk or Opportunity, 1988 (Box 79)
    - Presentations, 1988 and 1990, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Seven-Up
    - General files, 1956 Aug.-1959 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 79)
    - Background information, 1989 (Box 80)
    - Clippings, 1989 (Box 80)
    - Commercial scripts, 1989 (Box 80)
    - Research, 1989 (Box 80)
    - Uncola campaign, 1973 (Box 80)
  - Shaw-Walker Company
    - General files, 1952 June-1961 July (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 80)
  - Sherwin-Williams
    - Getting Involved presentation, 1983-1987 (Box 80)
    - Where is Sherwin-Williams? presentation, 1983 (Box 80)
  - ShopKo Stores, Incorporated
    - Questionnaire response, 1985 (Box 80)
  - Showtime
    - Agency presentation fact book, 1984 (Box 80)
    - Credentials presentation, circa 1986 (Box 80)
  - Singer Sewing Machines
    - General files, 1952 June-1967 Apr. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 80)
  - Six Flags
    - General files, 1985 Penetration tracking study, 1987 (Box 80)
    - Presentation, 1987 (Box 80)
    - Proposal, 1984 (Box 81)
  - Smirnoff (Diageo)
    - [Project 21 (JWT/42 Entertainment), circa 2005: Moved to Restricted Materials] (Box 81)
  - Sony
    - General files, includes campaign notes, 1986-1987 (Box 81)
    - Credentials presentation, 1978 (Box 81)
  - Speedy Muffler King
    - JWT local market buying presentation, undated (Box 81)
    - J. Walter Speedy presentation, circa 1987 (Box 81)
    - Toronto presentation file, 1987 July 14-15 (Box 81)
    - What Business Are We In? presentation, undated (Box 81)
    - Winning in the Marketplace--Tune-up Manufacturers Institute presentation, undated (Box 81)
  - Sprint
    - Annual report, fact book, 1993 (Box 81)
    - Creative guidelines, 1986 (Box 81)
    - General creative files, 1990 (Box 81)
    - JWT presentation, 1986 Apr. 1 (Box 81)
    - Long distance category overview--major historical milestones, 1994 (Box 81)
    - Marketing profile of U.S. Sprint, 1985 (Box 81)
    - Presentation, 1984 Feb. 29 (Box 81)
    - Presentation, 1986, 3 folders (Box 82)
    - Research findings, 1984 (Box 82)
    - Subscriber and non-subscriber attitudes toward Sprint, 1983 (Box 82)
    - Summary of Research Conducted for Sprint's Business Market, 1983 (Box 82)
    - U.S. Sprint's Strengths and Weaknesses, 1985 (Box 82)
    - Wall Street Journal special report on telecommunications, 1986, Feb. 24 (Box 82)
  - Squibb Beech-Nut
    - General files, 1968 Jan.-1968 Mar. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 82)
  - Staff Builders
    - Growth presentation, 1985 Nov. 5 (Box 82)
  - Standard Brands, Incorporated
    - General files, 1953 Mar.-1964 Jan. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 82)
  - Sterling Brewers
    - General files, 1962 Mar. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 82)
  - Stouffer's
    - Adapting to an Evolving Market, 1993 (Box 82)
    - Clippings, 1987 (Box 82)
    - Frozen entrees/dinners: What's Going On? presentation, 1987 (Box 82)
    - Frozen food entree, creative strategy and situation analysis, 1986 (Box 83)
    - Frozen food entree update, 1987 (Box 83)
    - Lean Cuisine
      - Presentations, 1983-1993, 4 folders (Box 83)
      - Stouffer's and competitive frozen food advertising, 1993 (Box 83)
  - Sun Microsystems
    - [Two of the World's Cooler Networks, 1994: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 83)
  - SunSweet
    - Sweet Partnership presentation, 1989 (Box 83)
  - Telecheck
    - Gaining Your Acceptance, circa 1991 (Box 83)
    - Leadership marketing, 1991 (Box 83)
  - Thomson-McKinnon Securities, Incorporated
    - General files, 1988 (Box 83)
    - Buying system, 1988 (Box 84)
    - Consumer's buying system, undated (Box 84)
    - Financial companies advertising spending, 1981-1987 (Box 84)
    - Presentation, 1988, 3 folders (Box 84)
  - Thomas A. Edison Industries
    - General files, 1957 Aug. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 84)
  - Today's Man
    - Building Market Dominance, 1992 Dec. 16 (Box 84)
    - Giving Today's Men What They Want, 1993 (Box 84)
    - Questionnaire, 1993 (Box 84)
    - Suiting Up For Today's Man, 1993 (Box 84)
  - Trailways--East Coast Group
    - General files, 1960 July-Aug. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 84)
  - Umbro
    - Owning Football, 1995 (Box 85)
  - Unilever
    - Food Advertising in the United States, 1982 (Box 85)